swadesi.com 2012-04-13

# Privacy Policy

Information is the core of our business at the Micro Equity Development Fund (“MEDF”). This Privacy Policy explains how the MEDF collects, uses, and discloses the personal information you may provide while using the MEDF’s web site (www.themedf.org). 

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data management and security measures.

We, the MEDF, will never rent or sell your personal information to third parties. We will not disclose your personally identifiable activity to any third party without your consent. We restrict access to personal information to MEDF employees and entities that need to know that information in order to manage, develop or improve our service. These individuals are bound by legal confidentiality and may be subject to discipline, including immediate termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

Also, the MEDF will regularly update you on the status of your account, so you may always be aware of developments and account activity.

MEDF reserves the right to record and display anonymous investment activity on our Website and display the general regions where our entrepreneurs and other parties are located.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to email us or write to us at:

_Privacy Support  
c/o MEDF.  
21 Kirkland Drive  
Cambridge, Massachusetts, 02138  
USA_
